{
    "subject": "resource/Edward_Garnier",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/Jesus_College,_Oxford",
    "human_readable": "Edward Garnier was educated at Jesus College, Oxford.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8633930087089539,
            "question": "What is the name of the college that educated Edward Garnier?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.827003002166748,
            "question": "What college is associated with Edward Garnier's education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8185579180717468,
            "question": "Where did Edward Garnier receive his education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7856560349464417,
            "question": "At which university did Edward Garnier study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7642213106155396,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Edward Garnier's life after completing his studies at Jesus College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7318653464317322,
            "question": "Did Edward Garnier attend any other educational institutions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7219365835189819,
            "question": "What are some notable alumni from Jesus College, Oxford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5569855570793152,
            "question": "Are there any records of Edward Garnier's academic achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5498693585395813,
            "question": "Is there information available about Edward Garnier's field of study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38546648621559143,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Edward Garnier's family or personal background?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edward Garnier was educated at Jesus College, Oxford.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2658_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there information available about Edward Garnier's field of study?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2658_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any records of Edward Garnier's academic achievements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2658_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable alumni from Jesus College, Oxford?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2658_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2658_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2658_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2658_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2658_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2658_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2658_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2658_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2658_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2658_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2658_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n* The first document mentions Edward Garnier being educated at Wellington College, Berkshire, and Jesus College, Oxford.\n* The third document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2658/re-ranker-msmarco/34.txt) also confirms that Edward Garnier was educated at Jesus College, Oxford.\n\nBased on this information, I can conclude that the statement \"Edward Garnier was educated at Jesus College, Oxford\" is supported by the documents.\n\nTherefore, my response in JSON format would be:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis response is based on the provided context information which explicitly states that \"Edward Garnier was educated at Wellington College, Berkshire, Jesus College, Oxford, and the College of Law, London.\" Therefore, the query correctly attributes part of Edward Garnier's educational background."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}